Contact

allisonwade44@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/allison-wadea2a817b4 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

EMR

Critical Care

HIPAA

Languages

English

Certifications

Advanced Burn Life Support NIH Stroke Scale Certifications A, B, C, & D

Allison Wade

Emergency Room Nurse at New Hanover Regional Medical Center Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Eight + years of nursing experience to include: Clinical trials management in Acute Myeloid Leukemia, MDS, Hairy Cell Leukemia. Level 1 Trauma ER, Interventional Radiology, PreOp-PACU, & Free standing emergency center experience. CEN & TCRN

Experience

New Hanover Regional Medical Center Emergency Room Nurse July 2020 - Present (1 month) Wilmington, North Carolina, United States

SignatureCare Emergency Center Registered Nurse June 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months) Houston, Texas

UT MD Anderson Cancer Center - Cancer Prevention Research
Training Program
Research Nurse
February 2018 - July 2020 (2 years 6 months)
Houston, Texas

River Oaks Surgical Center Registered Nurse Pre Op/ PACU October 2016 - January 2018 (1 year 4 months) PreOp- PACU

Sacred Heart Emergency Center Registered Nurse, Emergency October 2014 - April 2017 (2 years 7 months) Houston, Texas

Work independently with one Physician and Radiology technologist in seven bed private emergency center.

CHI St. Luke's Health - Baylor St. Luke's Medical Center Registered Nurse, Interventional Radiology January 2015 - December 2015 (1 year) Houston, Texas

Magnet Facility. Neurovascular interventional radiology, angiography, MRI, CT, Ultrasound, Xray.

Vidant Medical Center Registered Nurse Emergency Department February 2012 - August 2014 (2 years 7 months) Greenville, North Carolina

BCEN. Magnet Facility. 58 bed level I trauma center, stroke center, stroke team member, administering TPA in department & well as during patient transport.

Education

East Carolina University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2008 - 2011)